The country folks does not look
the same after this. Not trying
to be alarmist here but it
doesn't look the same. It does
not emerge in the same way. If
you're still thinking in terms
of left or right, Republican or
Democrat in this period of
time, you're wrong. You're
wrong and I feel bad for you
because you're going to step on
your throat. Um it has nothing
to do with the blue or red or
Republican or Democrat left or
right, that is a show and the
country is unprepared for
what's about to happen. There's
no way to be prepared for
what's about to happen. What's
about to happen is going to be
truly astounding for a lot of
people. We're all going to know
people who pass away tragically
from this disease. It's
going to be emotionally
scarring. It's going to damage
the psyche of people. Not only
individually but the country
psyche. And I think
unfortunately the reality of
how bad things are is going to
push people further into their
own world. Some of you have no
clue what's coming because you
trust the government and the
media because your children or
you're insane. They know things
we don't know. They're trying
to avoid widespread panic.
They're trying to avoid chaos.
They know this is a lot worse
than they're even letting on.
So we have the Vice President
going yeah most people don't
have anything to worry about
when contracting this disease.
There are no numbers to support
that. We don't know that that's
the case. We don't know. What's
a death toll in Italy right
now? 4, 825 B. And it's not
over. I know you know if we if
we if we were closing the
Buckeye people go four
thousand. So what? I don't know
anybody with coronavirus. Do
you know how many people die of
gunshot wounds? You know how
many people die of other
things? Like the flu? This
isn't over. We're just
beginning. The movie has just
started. We're barely through
the previews. We have a
worldwide preventable pandemic
in this country. A stock market
crash likes which we haven't
seen in a generation and we're
going into a global depression.
And Trump may still win. He
might pull it out. He the
record he has to run on is the
worst record of any maybe
president ever. I mean has
anyone the wholesale
destruction of the American
economy and our complete way of
life. We can't our houses. We
all the whole country got
suspended. Even me who realizes
and has realized that Trump
again is a hawkster. If you
don't see that even if you
think he's funny even if you
hate the other side you you see
Trump as a huckster I think the
difference is that a lot of
people out there go yeah but
he's our huckster he's my like
he's he's ripping off everybody
on behalf of us if that were
only the case if that were only
the case I could be like great
but you can't leave your house
because we didn't order the
tests and the masks Cuz he
didn't care. Cuz he didn't want
to spook the stock market by
even talking about a pandemic.
We don't need a lot of people
to die to unleash martial law
and to doom the economy. You
don't need a lot of people to
die to collapse the healthcare
system. I mean are we going to
be living under martial law and
still watching Jimmy Fallon? Is
that the what's going to happen
here? Are we going to be living
under martial law and still
watching Carpool Karaoke? Shut
it down. I mean Can you imagine
it? Jimmy Fallon going outside.
Ellen dancing with the
military. Jimmy Fallon taking
pictures with the tank that's
parked at the end of his block.
I mean at what point can we
just can we can we request that
they shut the entertainment
industry off? Shut it off.
There should be martial law on
Instagram. Every company in
this country right now should
be making ventilators.
Everybody and some of them are
to their credit. Every ****
company should be mahogandas.
Whoever. Make **** ventilators.
You're going to need a lot of
ventilators. You're going to
need masks. Make **** masks.
You know? This should have been
happening months ago. Then we
have where's Joe Biden by the
way? Where's Joe Biden? Has Joe
Biden? He's running for the
presidency. He's running for
the highest office in the land.
He's disappeared. He's he's
he's his handlers are keeping
him out of the spotlight. Cuz
they know he'll make a mess of
this. You know the next two to
three weeks going to tell us a
lot. They're going to tell us
if the healthcare system
completely collapses. They're
going to tell us if you know
Probably if we're heading into
more of a severe lockdown,
something that looks or not
that looks, that is a martial
law. Um these things are all on
the table I don't know that we
have to freak out about them
because you don't really have
control over them but the idea
of you know the election
getting pushed back or being
cancelled the idea that you
know come November people are
not going to be able or feel
comfortable voting getting the
other you know all these things
are are going to change our
lives for a foreseeable period
it's not conspiracy mongering
to say that we are you know in
you know the survival of the
country right now is not
guaranteed and I and I don't I
don't say that you know to joke
around and I don't say that to
be dramatic or to be an
alarmist the the survival of
the country that we are living
in right now in any and by the
way the country in the sense
that it looks or feels like
anything you remember is not
guaranteed. It's not. It's
truly not. The people at the
top know that. Uh we're at the
precipice of something very
very
and if you see huge spikes in
crime if you see a global
depression if you see a loss of
faith in the government which I
don't know how you don't see
more of I think it's because
people are afraid right now so
they're kind of ignoring
certain things the inside are
trading and stuff like that I
think people are you know you
know burying their heads in the
sand but if you see those
things happen I mean these
these are the ingredients that
you know bring about a fall.